<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><ProductInfo>
   <Details url="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=test&amp;creative=9441&amp;camp=1793&amp;link_code=xm2&amp;path=ASIN/B0000658CD">
      <Asin>B0000658CD</Asin>
      <ProductName>Toshiba e310 Pocket PC</ProductName>
      <Catalog>Electronics</Catalog>
      <Manufacturer>Toshiba</Manufacturer>
      <ImageUrlSmall>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B0000658CD.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlSmall>
      <ImageUrlMedium>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B0000658CD.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlMedium>
      <ImageUrlLarge>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B0000658CD.01.LZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlLarge>
      <ListPrice>$399.94</ListPrice>
      <OurPrice>$399.94</OurPrice>
      <ThirdPartyNewPrice>$422.14</ThirdPartyNewPrice>
      <SalesRank>14</SalesRank>
      <BrowseList>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Personal Digital Assistant (PDA, Electronic Organizer)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Pocket PC (PCs)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Casio</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handheld (Hand Held)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
      </BrowseList>
      <Media>Electronics</Media>
      <NumberofItems>1</NumberofItems>
      <Features>
         <Feature>Lightweight, ultra-thin Pocket PC loaded with productivity and entertainment applications</Feature>
         <Feature>Expandable via built-in Secure Digital (SD) slot</Feature>
         <Feature>32 MB RAM and 32 MB ROM ; 206 MHz Intel StrongARM 32-bit RISC processor</Feature>
         <Feature>240 x 320 pixel TFT LCD screen displays more than 64,000 colors</Feature>
         <Feature>Features Pocket PC 2002 operating system, with improved handwriting recognition and new versions of Pocket Outlook, Word, and Excel</Feature>
      </Features>
      <Availability>Available</Availability>
      <Upc>032017138018</Upc>
      <Accessories>
         <Accessory>B00005MISL</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005RZO4</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005RI8T</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005ICE0</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005AUX4</Accessory>
      </Accessories>
      <Reviews>
         <AverageRating>4.125</AverageRating>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>1</Rating>
            <Summary>Pointless</Summary>
            <Comment>There is absolutely no point - now that there are palmtops on the market that are far more functional - in a handheld that requires the use of a dinky little stylus and a specialized writing method to enter characters, and has a tiny little display window unsuited for any long form text.&lt;BR>Not to mention that it has an MS operating system, which I have some philosophical problems with.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>I would deny it...</Summary>
            <Comment>If you told my boss that I said this, I would deny it, but I didn't buy this e310 for work. This is the most fun that I have had with an electronic "work device" since I bought my first PC. I've been reluctant to convert to PDAs for a number of reasons, but the thin size, great price, Pocket PC software, and my experience with Toshiba portables were enough to get me to pitch my paper scheduler and give this Pocket PC a try. So far the conversion has been going just fine.&lt;P>There are so many +'s that I can't mention them all. I'm not just referring to the cool features built into the OS, but the Pocket PC itself has many mentionables; like the record button on the top left side that makes audio notes a cinch. The screen is a definite strength. The adjustable front-light makes the screen comfortably viewable in just about any setting. It makes sense to invest in the relatively expensive screen overlays, because they double as anti-glare protectors. I say that even though I have never successfully got one on without a bunch of the tiny air bubbles stuck under the surface.&lt;P>Thanks to Adobe you can enjoy reading pdf files anywhere you can take this.&lt;P>Some of the annoyances are that on first look it would seem that both the USB cable accessory, that is sold separately as a replacement for the cradle, and the power cable won't fit in the bottom at the same time, but at a closer look the power cable plugs into the USB cord, so you can charge while you sync without the cradle.&lt;P>I do hope that more networking options become available for the SD slot. Currently the BlueTooth compatible device is the only one listed for this PDA. I also wish the industry would decide on a PC Card standard so all our cameras, PDAs, and portables could share cards without depending on conversion. No external keyboard yet either.&lt;P>The LI-ION battery-life is OK. It depends on how much you use the thing. There is no external access to the battery which I find a little strange. Without being read on the matter, I figure that the battery is accessed by removing the back-plate.&lt;P>I am a bit afraid of that moment when this PDAs durability is tested. I've certainly felt more rugged feeling Pocket PCs. But who knows, Toshiba is full of surprises.&lt;P>On the topic of the OS, the default settings for the input word-selection, that's like a popup AutoComplete as you type, bugged me. I don't like that the popup words are usually the longest form of the word, so you seldom use them. Luckily, I found the way to increase the number of words that popup, which helped.&lt;P>I find Toshiba's e310 PDA more than easy, efficient, practical, compact, sleek and enjoyable to use, it's a blast!</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>Small, Fast and Sexy</Summary>
            <Comment>This is by far the best looking and thinest Pocket Pc available. I have bene useing it now for a couple weeks and have nothing to complain about.The battery life is ok.The screen is bright and can be read outside durign the day.The only drawback's would be the lack of a CF slot but the SD card slot compensates for that. It is smaller, better looking and just as fast as an IPAQ.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
      </Reviews>
      <Similarities>
         <Similarity>B00005ICE0</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00003CXI1</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005OWEG</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005O3VC</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005RG4O</Similarity>
      </Similarities>
   </Details>
   <Details url="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=test&amp;creative=9441&amp;camp=1793&amp;link_code=xm2&amp;path=ASIN/B00005V9B8">
      <Asin>B00005V9B8</Asin>
      <ProductName>iConcepts Universal PDA Starter Kit</ProductName>
      <Catalog>Electronics</Catalog>
      <Manufacturer>iConcepts</Manufacturer>
      <ImageUrlSmall>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005V9B8.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlSmall>
      <ImageUrlMedium>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005V9B8.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlMedium>
      <ImageUrlLarge>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005V9B8.01.LZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlLarge>
      <ListPrice>$29.99</ListPrice>
      <OurPrice>Too Low To Display</OurPrice>
      <SalesRank>211</SalesRank>
      <BrowseList>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Personal Digital Assistant (PDA, Electronic Organizer)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Palm IIIc (3c)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Stylus Pen (Styli)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Keyboards (Input Devices)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handheld (Hand Held)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Cases Covers</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Cleaners Kits Maintenance</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Palm IIIe (3e)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Palm v (5)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>(Input Devices)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Palm vii (7)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handspring Visor (Hand spring handspringvisor)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Storage Cases</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Styli, Stylus, pens</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Palm m100</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Keyboards (Keyboard)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Stylus (Styli)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Cleaners (Cleaner)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Kits (Kit)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Pocket PC (PCs)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Hewlett-Packard (Hewlett, Packard, HP)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Compaq</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Palm m500 m505</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
      </BrowseList>
      <Media>Electronics</Media>
      <NumberofItems>1</NumberofItems>
      <Features>
         <Feature>Everything you need to get you stared with your new PDA</Feature>
         <Feature>Pack of 6 screen protectors</Feature>
         <Feature>Wet/dry wipes</Feature>
         <Feature>Leather carrying case</Feature>
         <Feature>Universal 4-in-1 stylus</Feature>
      </Features>
      <Availability>Available</Availability>
      <Upc>071331704462</Upc>
      <Accessories>
         <Accessory>B00004ZB57</Accessory>
      </Accessories>
      <Reviews>
         <AverageRating>4.14286</AverageRating>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>Great case, stylus and more for good price</Summary>
            <Comment>Finally something of "all in one" types of products for maintaining your Personal Digital Assistant (PDA) for small price comparing to the price of items of same quality sold separately. I have Handspring and I found this product very useful because of great case of real hi-quality leather and multi functional stylus I felt in love with. I think that this product will satisfy needs of every owner of any type of PDA, never mind if it is Handspring, Palm, Sony, IBM or even Pocket PC. And I think that this is specially useful for those who recently bought new PDA and do not have time or will to experiment for choosing right case or spare styli, or as a gift for someone who spends time with PDA. I give it 5 stars.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>GREAT KIT !!!!</Summary>
            <Comment>EVERYTHING THAT CAME IN THE KIT WAS VERY USEFULL I WOULD RECOMMAND.I ESPECIALLY LIKED THE CASE AND THE SYTLUS.GRAET DEAL !!!!!!!!!!</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>Worth every Penny!!!</Summary>
            <Comment>I have been searching for an all in one package for my PDA and this kit has everything. It came with a genuine leather case which everybody sells for $... The 4 in 1 stylus is a great idea rather than carrying a stylus and pens. The screen protectors it came with 1 for my Palm however i just purchases a pack of 12 for $... (also a great deal). If you bought each item seperate it would cost alot more. All in all the kit is worth it!! </Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
      </Reviews>
      <Similarities>
         <Similarity>B00005ALB1</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005Y3V5</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005Y3V6</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004VWM3</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00003CXI1</Similarity>
      </Similarities>
   </Details>
   <Details url="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=test&amp;creative=9441&amp;camp=1793&amp;link_code=xm2&amp;path=ASIN/B00005O0IU">
      <Asin>B00005O0IU</Asin>
      <ProductName>Casio Cassiopeia BE-300 Pocket Manager 16MB Color</ProductName>
      <Catalog>Electronics</Catalog>
      <Mpn>BE-300</Mpn>
      <Manufacturer>Casio</Manufacturer>
      <ImageUrlSmall>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005O0IU.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlSmall>
      <ImageUrlMedium>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005O0IU.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlMedium>
      <ImageUrlLarge>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005O0IU.01.LZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlLarge>
      <ListPrice>$199.99</ListPrice>
      <OurPrice>$159.94</OurPrice>
      <UsedPrice>$152.94</UsedPrice>
      <ThirdPartyNewPrice>$205.37</ThirdPartyNewPrice>
      <SalesRank>225</SalesRank>
      <BrowseList>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Personal Digital Assistant (PDA, Electronic Organizer)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Pocket PC (PCs)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Casio</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handheld (Hand Held)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
      </BrowseList>
      <Media>Electronics</Media>
      <NumberofItems>1</NumberofItems>
      <Features>
         <Feature>16 MB of internal RAM</Feature>
         <Feature>3.2-inch color display</Feature>
         <Feature>320 by 240 screen resolution</Feature>
         <Feature>Runs on Windows CE 3.0</Feature>
         <Feature>USB client support</Feature>
      </Features>
      <Platform>Windows NT</Platform>
      <Availability>Special Order</Availability>
      <Upc>079767696948</Upc>
      <Accessories>
         <Accessory>B00000JDK3</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00004TEN2</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005AC8J</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00004SZ9K</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00003G1RE</Accessory>
      </Accessories>
      <Reviews>
         <AverageRating>3.9</AverageRating>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>2</Rating>
            <Summary>I want my Palm back!!!</Summary>
            <Comment>I've had my Cassiopeia for close to 9 months now. Prior to having the Cassiopeia I was a Palm user. I more or less depend on having my calendar, contacts, notes, etc. with me all of the time. I made the decision (and it was a tough decision) to switch to the Cassiopeia/Windows CE platform because of the following things that the Palm didn't offer. I've been constantly disappointed.&lt;P>-Ability to sync with outlook mail: It works great, however you can't sync email if you're syncing with more than 1 computer (i.e. home computer and office computer) so it's useless to me.&lt;P>-Ability to access personal financial sites: Many of the web sites that I want access to when traveling are my bank accounts. I can't access them because Pocket Explorer is not the "correct" version and does not have the correct level of security (even with the 128 bit patch), so my bank site will not allow access.&lt;P>-Ability to download and listen to audio books from Audible.com: The transfer process is so unbelievably slow I've given up and taking audio books with me when I travel. &lt;P>-Ability to read eBooks: Books from Peanut Press work fine with Peanut Reader. Books for Microsoft Reader are another story. Very disappointing.&lt;P>-Ability to synchronize with my MS Money accounts: This is perhaps the most infuriating bug of all. Good luck with keeping your accounts synced. Balances get screwed up and it's not uncommon for the Money file to come up corrupted, requiring you to replace the file and re-sync it. There's a whole list of procedures to remedy crashed money files, but I really don't feel like spending hours fixing something, over and over, that should have worked in the first place.&lt;P>Add to all of the above, appointments and contacts that magically vanish, only to reappear days later, and some of the worst customer support from Microsoft that I've ever experienced, this time-saving device is far too time-intensive. I regret ever letting go of my precious Palm!</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>CTRL Q</Summary>
            <Comment>After going through weeks of deliberation (for a pocket PC)and a couple of hands on testing sessions of both the Ipaq (disPLAY model in CompUsa, I love NYC) and the E 125, I finally chose the the Cassiopeia.&lt;P>Here's why:&lt;P>1). Price. With the Ipaq 3650 you don't get the built in CF slot which adds at the least 50$ to the [$] base price. I found the Cassiopeia for [$] (with rebate) online with free 2nd day shipping. True the Ipaq wins in support and probable future add on gadgets through its sleeves, but those suckers cost $$.&lt;P>2). Replaceable Casio battery. Ipaq's battery lasts longer but the casio's batteries are replaceable. If you buy enough of these [$] batteries you could get a great deal of battery power. To be honest though, there exists a 4AA battery extender for the Ipaq/Casio for 20$ so this issue is not a big one for me.&lt;P>3). Games. Hardware button problem on the Ipaq might hamper future games (can't press two buttons at once). Casio is layed out like a gameboy.&lt;P>4). Ipaq has a great outdoor screen admittedly, but I rarely use PDAs in direct sunlight for extended periods (I do have to shade it). &lt;P>5). I don't understand why no one knows about shutting programs by bringing up the keyboard and hitting ctrl Q. Really easy.&lt;P>6). I was really scared off by the large amount of overall lapses in manufacturing quality of the Ipaq (dust under the screen even on the newer models, screen bugs, the popup stylus etc.) especially those on the discussion boards. The Ipaq is great but not quite there. The Ipaq 2 or 3 someday? Maybe. it's just scary to get something that costs so much only to have it in the shop most of the time. The cassiopeia has been around the block.&lt;P>7). Though the Ipaq cpu is faster, it's not always valid to compare speed with cpu Mhz. For example a 1.33 ghz Athlon desktop can out-benchmark a 1.5 ghz pentium depending on the system. 207 mHz is faster, don't get me wrong but 150mhz is far from slow.&lt;P>8). Looks. I plan on using CF memory on my pocket PC so the CF slot is a must. I'm not overly concerned with looks and don't think it should be THE deciding factor. Indeed, the Ipaq is very pretty but it loses something with it's expansion sleeves on. Though there are some nice looking custom cf sleeves they are very expensive. &lt;P>That's my two cents hope this helps.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>2</Rating>
            <Summary>Not for medical people</Summary>
            <Comment>The color and graphics are great - however the only software you can use - is that made for the BE-300 strictly. Windows CE based software with not work, at least I haven't found the trick yet. I bought the BE-300, thinking it would work for my medical software - boy I was wrong. Now I strictly use the BE-300 for addresses and to play games. I contacted Cassio via email several times and never received a reply to any of my questions I think there's a Handspring or Palm in my near future. If anyone has some helpful suggestions - please post them.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
      </Reviews>
      <Similarities>
         <Similarity>B0000513UE</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004T2LJ</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004T2LG</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B000059WDL</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00003G1RG</Similarity>
      </Similarities>
   </Details>
   <Details url="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=test&amp;creative=9441&amp;camp=1793&amp;link_code=xm2&amp;path=ASIN/B00005AKV3">
      <Asin>B00005AKV3</Asin>
      <ProductName>Compaq iPAQ Compact Flash Card Expansion Pack</ProductName>
      <Catalog>Electronics</Catalog>
      <Mpn>170339-b22</Mpn>
      <Manufacturer>Compaq</Manufacturer>
      <ImageUrlSmall>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005AKV3.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlSmall>
      <ImageUrlMedium>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005AKV3.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlMedium>
      <ImageUrlLarge>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005AKV3.01.LZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlLarge>
      <ListPrice>$39.99</ListPrice>
      <OurPrice>$39.94</OurPrice>
      <SalesRank>108</SalesRank>
      <BrowseList>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Personal Digital Assistant (PDA, Electronic Organizer)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Pocket PC (PCs)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Compaq</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handheld (Hand Held)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
      </BrowseList>
      <Media>Electronics</Media>
      <NumberofItems>1</NumberofItems>
      <Features>
         <Feature>Increases the functionality of your iPAQ Pocket PC</Feature>
         <Feature>Adds a CompactFlash expansion slot</Feature>
         <Feature>Permits plug-in storage cards and LAN connectivity</Feature>
         <Feature>Can be used to connect modems or bar code scanners made by other manufacturers</Feature>
         <Feature>Easy to install; stylish and lightweight</Feature>
      </Features>
      <Availability>Special Order</Availability>
      <Upc>720591550394</Upc>
      <Accessories>
         <Accessory>B00005IAYA</Accessory>
      </Accessories>
      <Reviews>
         <AverageRating>4.33333</AverageRating>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>Highly Desired Accessory.</Summary>
            <Comment>The single compact flash expansion sleeve is a minimal way to go for expanding your iPAQ. The iPAQ can play mp3's directly off compact flash, there are a lot of available expansions for compact flash.&lt;P>It might be wiser to look at one of the "PC card expansion sleeves" as they include an extra battery! You can pick up Compact Flash adaptors for PC cards cheep, like under ten US dollars.&lt;P>Compact Flash memory can be found at fairly low prices.&lt;P>With this expansion installed - the protective cover which comes with the iPAC 3765 is a fairly tight fit.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>4</Rating>
            <Summary>Good...But big</Summary>
            <Comment>Before I begin, I love my iPaq. However, this is my biggest gripe with the iPaq, they need this expansion pack to throw a CF card into them. Without it, the iPaq is small and sleek; with it, it's huge. And, with the sheer amount of stuff out there with Compact Flash connectivity (modem, networking, CF cards, etc), I think it is inane that Compaq didn't at least include it with the iPaq. Or, better yet, build a CF slot into the machine. &lt;P>Still, it is necessary for what I think is the best PDA on the market. While I think the idea is dumb, it works great and isn't all that expensive. Hence my 4 star rating</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>4</Rating>
            <Summary>Works great but doesn't fit in a case</Summary>
            <Comment>I bought this Expansion pack when i bought my new Compaq Ipaq 3765. I have used it for about a month now and i really like it. The Ipaq fits in it very well and it does make the Ipaq easier to hold when i am walking around the office or at home answering email or surfing the net. I use a Linksys compact flash 802.11b card plugged into this sleeve to connect to my company's intranet I do have a problem with the size in that none of the cases will hold the Ipaq with the expansion slot on. This makes it a little hard because when i leave the office i have to take the sleeve off to put the unit in its case for the trip home, or take the chance of scratching the face of the Ipaq. I am kind of worried about how long the connector will last with this kind of use. &lt;BR>Over all it is a very good product. I have not had any problems with this piece and for the price it is worth it... you won't go wrong.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
      </Reviews>
      <Similarities>
         <Similarity>B0000488VI</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004T2LJ</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004T3F8</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00003G1RG</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005AC8J</Similarity>
      </Similarities>
   </Details>
   <Details url="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=test&amp;creative=9441&amp;camp=1793&amp;link_code=xm2&amp;path=ASIN/B00005QEYI">
      <Asin>B00005QEYI</Asin>
      <ProductName>Compaq iPAQ 3835 Color Pocket PC</ProductName>
      <Catalog>Electronics</Catalog>
      <Mpn>230397-002</Mpn>
      <Manufacturer>Compaq</Manufacturer>
      <ImageUrlSmall>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005QEYI.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlSmall>
      <ImageUrlMedium>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005QEYI.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlMedium>
      <ImageUrlLarge>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005QEYI.01.LZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlLarge>
      <ListPrice>$599.99</ListPrice>
      <OurPrice>Too Low To Display</OurPrice>
      <UsedPrice>$450.00</UsedPrice>
      <RefurbishedPrice>$430.00</RefurbishedPrice>
      <ThirdPartyNewPrice>$639.00</ThirdPartyNewPrice>
      <SalesRank>102</SalesRank>
      <BrowseList>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Personal Digital Assistant (PDA, Electronic Organizer)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Pocket PC (PCs)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Compaq</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handheld (Hand Held)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Casio</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
      </BrowseList>
      <Media>Electronics</Media>
      <NumberofItems>1</NumberofItems>
      <Features>
         <Feature>Pocket PC 2002 operating system features improved handwriting recognition and new versions of Pocket Outlook, Word, and Excel</Feature>
         <Feature>64 MB RAM and 32 MB ROM ; 206 MHz Intel StrongARM 32-bit RISC processor</Feature>
         <Feature>240 x 320-inch TFT LCD screen displays more than 4,000 colors</Feature>
         <Feature>Built-in Secure Digital card slot for adding more memory</Feature>
         <Feature>Pre-installed software includes Pocket Word, Pocket Excel, Pocket Internet Explorer, Windows Media Player (MP3), Inbox (e-mail), Microsoft Reader (e-boks), and more</Feature>
      </Features>
      <Platform>Windows 2000</Platform>
      <Availability>Special Order</Availability>
      <Upc>720591705008</Upc>
      <Accessories>
         <Accessory>B00005ICDX</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005ICE0</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005MISL</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005UEA6</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005LCTY</Accessory>
      </Accessories>
      <Reviews>
         <AverageRating>3.96</AverageRating>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>4</Rating>
            <Summary>Pricey, but...</Summary>
            <Comment>After having been a dedicated palm user for the last 5 years it finally became time for me to get a new PDA. After shopping around a fair amount I finally decided on the iPaq 3835.&lt;P>I've had it for just over a month now and I have to say I'm quite impressed. Not only is the software far better than the standard Palm applications, the speed and memory storage simply blow away the last Palm I owned (a Palm V.)&lt;P>More significant than the better applications on the iPaq is its user input capabilities. Not only does the iPaq support a keyboard and a Palm-style graffiti interface, it also supports true handwriting input (script or block letters). Plus seeing the input drawn on the screen (rather than on an 'input area' off screen like the Palm uses) makes it that much easier. Add in the 'auto word completion' feature of the iPaq and input becomes a breeze.&lt;P>The downside? These features come at a price. Both literally, as the unit is roughly twice as expensive as a Palm, and in terms of the unit's size. It's roughly twice as heavy &amp; thick as a Palm.&lt;P>Still, after weighing (no pun intended) the benefits of each I chose the iPaq and I'm far happier with it than I ever was with my palm.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>3</Rating>
            <Summary>Typical Microsoft Operating System</Summary>
            <Comment>I went from a Palm PDA (Palm OS) to a Compaq IPAQ 3835 because I think the color and features are superior than Palm, and they are in the 3835. HOWEVER, I really miss the Palm OS, it is the best around. Microsoft cannot get it right even in a Pocket PC. The first day I had the 3835 it locked up on me and I had to do a soft reset. Never happened with a Palm. Several soft resets later... Today I loaded Dashboard software from the disc that Compaq sends with the 3835 and everything went haywire. It was so locked up I had to do my first (and I am sure not last) HARD reset! I wish the US Government people would do away with Microsoft and Bill Gates. He belongs sweeping floors somewhere! Why doesn't Palm come out with an OS for computers?</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>4</Rating>
            <Summary>Great Job, Compaq, but...</Summary>
            <Comment>I've used the iPaq 3635, 3765, and now, the 3835. I am quite an iPaq loyalist, and I love their new outing with the product line.&lt;P>The screen, for a obsessive compulsive like myself, allows for much greater color contrast, and minimizes on the grain when viewing digital images.&lt;P>I also love their decision to stick with the same form factor as the previous models; it works with previous expansion sleeves, and it still reigns as the BEST handheld. This is the first handheld that I can just hold in my hand, and it feels awesome to hold.&lt;P>I love their addition of the SD card slot on the top, but I feel somewhat cheated (here's where it lost a star). There are considerably smaller machines that offer the same as Compaq does with this device. I would have expected maybe an integrated CF slot? Integrated Wi-Fi? Although the more expensive model offers bluetooth, I'm sure alot more people would like to see a built in Wi-Fi chipset.&lt;P>To end on a good note, I've found that the new battery they have used adds a significant amount of battery life. In fact, I have found that my iPaq charges faster, and discharges about 20%-25% slower. Great job, guys. I also like the new software they have built in, allowing for something like 14 different backlight settings, and a percentage viewer for remaining battery life.&lt;P>I strongly reccomend the iPaq as your next purchase, but with the impending release of Xscale based systems, you might want to save your money for the new HP iPaqs.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
      </Reviews>
      <Similarities>
         <Similarity>B00005AKV3</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005AKV6</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005MOTE</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004T3F8</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005O76B</Similarity>
      </Similarities>
   </Details>
   <Details url="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=test&amp;creative=9441&amp;camp=1793&amp;link_code=xm2&amp;path=ASIN/B00004TF4D">
      <Asin>B00004TF4D</Asin>
      <ProductName>Sumdex Leather Palm Organizer Wallet</ProductName>
      <Catalog>Electronics</Catalog>
      <Manufacturer>Sumdex</Manufacturer>
      <ImageUrlSmall>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00004TF4D.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlSmall>
      <ImageUrlMedium>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00004TF4D.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlMedium>
      <ImageUrlLarge>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00004TF4D.01.LZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlLarge>
      <ListPrice>$19.95</ListPrice>
      <OurPrice>$8.54</OurPrice>
      <UsedPrice>$9.06</UsedPrice>
      <ThirdPartyNewPrice>$9.06</ThirdPartyNewPrice>
      <SalesRank>160</SalesRank>
      <BrowseList>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Personal Digital Assistant (PDA, Electronic Organizer)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Palm IIIe (3e)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Cases Covers</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handheld (Hand Held)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handspring Visor (Hand spring handspringvisor)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Storage Cases</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Pocket PC (PCs)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Casio</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Hewlett-Packard (Hewlett, Packard, HP)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Compaq</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
      </BrowseList>
      <Media>Electronics</Media>
      <NumberofItems>1</NumberofItems>
      <Features>
         <Feature>PDA compartment fits most organizers</Feature>
         <Feature>Includes credit card and checkbook compartments</Feature>
         <Feature>Zipper closure</Feature>
         <Feature>Elastic holders for spare batteries</Feature>
         <Feature>Lifetime warranty</Feature>
      </Features>
      <Availability>Special Order</Availability>
      <Upc>751530802717</Upc>
      <Reviews>
         <AverageRating>4.4186</AverageRating>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>Great case, great deal, great price</Summary>
            <Comment>I love this case! First of all, it looks great. It's good quality leather and the Sumdex logo is relatively unobtrusive on the front. I like the zipper enclosure, because even though it includes a Velcro strip to stick on the back of your PDA I don't have to use it (thereby marring the back of my new visor) because the zipper keeps it from falling out. &lt;P>Another reviewer said the case was too snug for his Visor. I have a Handspring Visor Deluxe and mine fits just fine. The only way the fit is a little snug is when I keep the plastic cover on (that came with the visor), but this way I don't have to worry about any possible battery drain or scratches on the screen. &lt;P>Though I have yet to drop my visor in its new case, I have no doubt that it would survive just fine. The leather on the front and back is fairly stiff on the inside (perhaps due to cardboard inserts?) but still slightly padded to the touch on the outside. The corners are rounded for comfort but still very sturdy ( I can't even make them bend myself). All this, added to the fact that it has card slots, elastic loops for holding batteries or an extra stylus, and a *cheap* price means it's a great deal that shouldn't be passed up.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>4</Rating>
            <Summary>Good value, but has some flaws</Summary>
            <Comment>First of all, let me say that the price for this case is unbeatable. It's low enough to not feel that the case needs to be coddled (thereby needing to protect the PDA's protection!?!) and yet you still get a nice-feeling leather case with a great zipper enclosure.&lt;P>However, I did run into the problem of it draining the batteries of my Handspring Visor Deluxe unless I leave the plastic cover on while in the case. This cover can be irritating when using the PDA, so I often leave it at home. This is big mistake with this case if you don't want to drain your batteries, though. The velcro attachment is also a little less elegant than other attachments I've seen (i.e. the Handspring cases).&lt;P>In short, this is a great case/wallet for the money. However, it's a little tight and can drain your batteries mighty quick.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>2</Rating>
            <Summary>Visor deluxe - problems with it</Summary>
            <Comment>I have a visor deluxe and after reading all these good reviews I went with this cheap case. Well, the minute I opened it I noticed the nylon-ish sides blooming out of the sides, quite unattractive I thought. But, who cares, it was leather and did a good job right? The next problem was with the velcro holding device. You must glue the velcro patch to your PDA's back (which is tricky enough with springboard covers and batteries in the way) and plus it makes the pda quite ugly and less sleek to hold. Then, inside the case, it wobbles on the velcro stip's thickness. It rides pretty high, too, and doesn't feel "locked in"&lt;P>I was about ready to deal with all of this since the case did fit the twist stylus/pen i bought nicely, but then the true problem arose: *The velcro prevents the unit from slipping into the hotsynch cradle since it must rest nicely on the slot in the back of the unit*&lt;P>So, this made it utterly useless! Hats off to sumdex. I'll give it one extra star for price.&lt;P>Jon</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
      </Reviews>
      <Similarities>
         <Similarity>B00003G1RG</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004SZ9M</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005AAKY</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004TF4C</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004WHF9</Similarity>
      </Similarities>
   </Details>
   <Details url="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=test&amp;creative=9441&amp;camp=1793&amp;link_code=xm2&amp;path=ASIN/B00005AMDE">
      <Asin>B00005AMDE</Asin>
      <ProductName>Targus Stowaway Portable Keyboard for Compaq iPAQ Pocket PCs</ProductName>
      <Catalog>Electronics</Catalog>
      <Manufacturer>Targus</Manufacturer>
      <ImageUrlSmall>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005AMDE.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlSmall>
      <ImageUrlMedium>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005AMDE.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlMedium>
      <ImageUrlLarge>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005AMDE.01.LZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlLarge>
      <ListPrice>$99.94</ListPrice>
      <OurPrice>$71.94</OurPrice>
      <UsedPrice>$69.99</UsedPrice>
      <RefurbishedPrice>$63.00</RefurbishedPrice>
      <ThirdPartyNewPrice>$89.03</ThirdPartyNewPrice>
      <SalesRank>312</SalesRank>
      <BrowseList>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Personal Digital Assistant (PDA, Electronic Organizer)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Pocket PC (PCs)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Compaq</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handheld (Hand Held)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
      </BrowseList>
      <Media>Electronics</Media>
      <NumberofItems>1</NumberofItems>
      <Features>
         <Feature>Full-size QWERTY keyboard</Feature>
         <Feature>Folds to fit in your pocket</Feature>
         <Feature>Built-in dock eliminates tangle of cables</Feature>
         <Feature>Includes short-cut keys that link directly to Inbox/Notes, Contacts/Word, Calendar/Excel, and Tasks/Money applications</Feature>
         <Feature>Compatible with Compaq iPAQ 3100, 3600, and 3700 series Pocket PCs; see Product Description for 3800 series compatibility</Feature>
      </Features>
      <Availability>Special Order</Availability>
      <Upc>092636108069</Upc>
      <Accessories>
         <Accessory>B000059TF8</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00004S7RC</Accessory>
      </Accessories>
      <Reviews>
         <AverageRating>4.52586</AverageRating>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>You've GOT TO HAVE THIS</Summary>
            <Comment>Even the packaging is awesome... but most of all, the functionality is supreme.&lt;P>The keyboard closes to form it's own strong protective casing... I have mine flopping around lose in my purse and it still works like a champ.&lt;P>Folded up, it's not much bigger than the Handspring in the leather case.&lt;P>Everytime I take out my keyboard in a meeting, at least one person in the meeting will say outloud, "WOW... what is that thing, and where did you get it?!"&lt;P>I've recommended it to a number of people who have bought their own and are thrilled with it.&lt;P>I can't say enough about how handy it is with taking notes.&lt;P>To take down a quick note, I'll still just use grafitti, but I've been in meetings where I've been asked to take minutes and I can't imagine having to do that w/ a stylus. No matter how fast you get w/ a stylus, it can't match the speed of typing.&lt;P>The keyboard stretches out to accommodate normal adult human hands which is a treat.&lt;P>My wish is that they come out w/ a new version that has a 10-key set as well... it would be a nice option for those who don't mind having one that's a little bigger. I'm always having to jot down IP addresses and other numeric data, and having to use the regular number buttons above the letters is a bit tedious. Otherwise, I highly recommend this.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>4</Rating>
            <Summary>instant laptop</Summary>
            <Comment>This keyboard turns a PDA into a poor man's laptop. If most of what you need it for is document driven, it's fantastic. I can type almost as fast as on my desktop, and with Wordsmith (an inexpensive but pretty powerful word processing program), I can create full length documents to review. Niceties such as spell checking and grammar (etc) can be done after syncing with a PC. I've been using this as a substitute for a pad at some meetings.&lt;P>A couple of caveats. I've seen some reviews that say that the Stowaway will work on your lap. I wouldn't advise it. The parts feel rather delicate--particularly the connection point. Use a table or, if you think you'll be doing lots of lap typing, go with GOTYPE. If space is a concern and you normally have meetings at tables, then this should be fine. (Moreover, there's a "gee whiz" factor to consider. The thing is just cool). Second, because of the small screen, one can write long documents, but it becomes tedious to read them. Bookmarking functions ameliorate this problem, but don't cure it. &lt;P>Still, it's obvious that a lot of thought went into the design of this product, and it pays off. The keys have good tactile response, and the function and shortcut keys were well thought out. If you have the cash and the inclination, definitely worth the money.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>4</Rating>
            <Summary>Almost perfect.</Summary>
            <Comment>This keyboard is impressive. Though it is not practical for constant use, it is certainly the answer if you have large amounts of text to enter. (I would not jot down a phone number or address with it, but if I'm copying a recipe, taking notes, or writing e-mail, it's perfect.) Even though I have a great and small laptop, there are times when I want to be typing in thirty seconds and be done-and certainly not re-forming graffiti gaffes or trying to remember punctuation. The software is easy to install, and you get the hang of connecting it to your visor after a few times. It's particularly useful for third party applications that don't have a pc desktop interface; my checkbook program, for example, would otherwise have me do my week's collection of receipts with the stylus.&lt;P>For the keyboard-&lt;BR>PRO: *Full size, comfortable, responsive; has a nice, faint clicking sensation. *Attaches easily. *Truly compact. *Some function keys. *Flawless (in my experience) integration with the rest of the machine-not glitchy and doesn't seem to drain the batteries. *Kinda slick to whip it out in a meeting room. &lt;BR>CON: *It can't sit right on your lap, really. You have to put it on something flat. &lt;P>For the software-&lt;BR>PRO: *Easy installation. *Some nice controls for repeat rate, etc. *Compatible with non-keyboard use of the Visor whenever you prefer. If it's in the keyboard, the machine knows it-use of the stylus is not at all compromised.&lt;BR>CON: *You still have to use the stylus. You can't tab between fields, choose items from pop-up menus, scroll through lists, or other things those of us who are truly keyboard-dependent have come to expect.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
      </Reviews>
      <Similarities>
         <Similarity>B000059TF8</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00003G1RG</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005AC8J</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004T2LJ</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004SPC0</Similarity>
      </Similarities>
   </Details>
   <Details url="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=test&amp;creative=9441&amp;camp=1793&amp;link_code=xm2&amp;path=ASIN/B00004YNWQ">
      <Asin>B00004YNWQ</Asin>
      <ProductName>Targus Stowaway Portable Keyboard for HP Jornada Pocket PCs</ProductName>
      <Catalog>Electronics</Catalog>
      <Manufacturer>Targus</Manufacturer>
      <ImageUrlSmall>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00004YNWQ.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlSmall>
      <ImageUrlMedium>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00004YNWQ.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlMedium>
      <ImageUrlLarge>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00004YNWQ.01.LZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlLarge>
      <ListPrice>$99.99</ListPrice>
      <OurPrice>$79.99</OurPrice>
      <UsedPrice>$75.00</UsedPrice>
      <ThirdPartyNewPrice>$82.66</ThirdPartyNewPrice>
      <SalesRank>381</SalesRank>
      <BrowseList>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Personal Digital Assistant (PDA, Electronic Organizer)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Pocket PC (PCs)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Hewlett-Packard (Hewlett, Packard, HP)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handheld (Hand Held)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
      </BrowseList>
      <Media>Electronics</Media>
      <NumberofItems>1</NumberofItems>
      <Features>
         <Feature>Full-size keyboard that fits in your pocket</Feature>
         <Feature>Compatible with Jornada Pocket PCs (520, 540, and 560 series)</Feature>
         <Feature>Shortcut and function keys for efficiency</Feature>
         <Feature>Special keys link directly to most-used applications</Feature>
         <Feature>Built-in dock eliminates cables</Feature>
      </Features>
      <Availability>Special Order</Availability>
      <Upc>092636100544</Upc>
      <Accessories>
         <Accessory>B000059TF8</Accessory>
      </Accessories>
      <Reviews>
         <AverageRating>4.52586</AverageRating>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>You've GOT TO HAVE THIS</Summary>
            <Comment>Even the packaging is awesome... but most of all, the functionality is supreme.&lt;P>The keyboard closes to form it's own strong protective casing... I have mine flopping around lose in my purse and it still works like a champ.&lt;P>Folded up, it's not much bigger than the Handspring in the leather case.&lt;P>Everytime I take out my keyboard in a meeting, at least one person in the meeting will say outloud, "WOW... what is that thing, and where did you get it?!"&lt;P>I've recommended it to a number of people who have bought their own and are thrilled with it.&lt;P>I can't say enough about how handy it is with taking notes.&lt;P>To take down a quick note, I'll still just use grafitti, but I've been in meetings where I've been asked to take minutes and I can't imagine having to do that w/ a stylus. No matter how fast you get w/ a stylus, it can't match the speed of typing.&lt;P>The keyboard stretches out to accommodate normal adult human hands which is a treat.&lt;P>My wish is that they come out w/ a new version that has a 10-key set as well... it would be a nice option for those who don't mind having one that's a little bigger. I'm always having to jot down IP addresses and other numeric data, and having to use the regular number buttons above the letters is a bit tedious. Otherwise, I highly recommend this.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>4</Rating>
            <Summary>instant laptop</Summary>
            <Comment>This keyboard turns a PDA into a poor man's laptop. If most of what you need it for is document driven, it's fantastic. I can type almost as fast as on my desktop, and with Wordsmith (an inexpensive but pretty powerful word processing program), I can create full length documents to review. Niceties such as spell checking and grammar (etc) can be done after syncing with a PC. I've been using this as a substitute for a pad at some meetings.&lt;P>A couple of caveats. I've seen some reviews that say that the Stowaway will work on your lap. I wouldn't advise it. The parts feel rather delicate--particularly the connection point. Use a table or, if you think you'll be doing lots of lap typing, go with GOTYPE. If space is a concern and you normally have meetings at tables, then this should be fine. (Moreover, there's a "gee whiz" factor to consider. The thing is just cool). Second, because of the small screen, one can write long documents, but it becomes tedious to read them. Bookmarking functions ameliorate this problem, but don't cure it. &lt;P>Still, it's obvious that a lot of thought went into the design of this product, and it pays off. The keys have good tactile response, and the function and shortcut keys were well thought out. If you have the cash and the inclination, definitely worth the money.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>4</Rating>
            <Summary>Almost perfect.</Summary>
            <Comment>This keyboard is impressive. Though it is not practical for constant use, it is certainly the answer if you have large amounts of text to enter. (I would not jot down a phone number or address with it, but if I'm copying a recipe, taking notes, or writing e-mail, it's perfect.) Even though I have a great and small laptop, there are times when I want to be typing in thirty seconds and be done-and certainly not re-forming graffiti gaffes or trying to remember punctuation. The software is easy to install, and you get the hang of connecting it to your visor after a few times. It's particularly useful for third party applications that don't have a pc desktop interface; my checkbook program, for example, would otherwise have me do my week's collection of receipts with the stylus.&lt;P>For the keyboard-&lt;BR>PRO: *Full size, comfortable, responsive; has a nice, faint clicking sensation. *Attaches easily. *Truly compact. *Some function keys. *Flawless (in my experience) integration with the rest of the machine-not glitchy and doesn't seem to drain the batteries. *Kinda slick to whip it out in a meeting room. &lt;BR>CON: *It can't sit right on your lap, really. You have to put it on something flat. &lt;P>For the software-&lt;BR>PRO: *Easy installation. *Some nice controls for repeat rate, etc. *Compatible with non-keyboard use of the Visor whenever you prefer. If it's in the keyboard, the machine knows it-use of the stylus is not at all compromised.&lt;BR>CON: *You still have to use the stylus. You can't tab between fields, choose items from pop-up menus, scroll through lists, or other things those of us who are truly keyboard-dependent have come to expect.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
      </Reviews>
      <Similarities>
         <Similarity>B000059TF8</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00003G1RG</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005AC8J</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004T2LJ</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004SPC0</Similarity>
      </Similarities>
   </Details>
   <Details url="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=test&amp;creative=9441&amp;camp=1793&amp;link_code=xm2&amp;path=ASIN/B00004SPC0">
      <Asin>B00004SPC0</Asin>
      <ProductName>Hewlett Packard Jornada 520 and 540 Series Screen Protectors</ProductName>
      <Catalog>Electronics</Catalog>
      <Manufacturer>Hewlett Packard</Manufacturer>
      <ImageUrlSmall>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00004SPC0.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlSmall>
      <ImageUrlMedium>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00004SPC0.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlMedium>
      <ImageUrlLarge>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00004SPC0.01.LZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlLarge>
      <ListPrice>$9.99</ListPrice>
      <OurPrice>$9.99</OurPrice>
      <UsedPrice>$7.00</UsedPrice>
      <ThirdPartyNewPrice>$8.72</ThirdPartyNewPrice>
      <SalesRank>431</SalesRank>
      <BrowseList>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>HP</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Hewlett Packard (Hewlett-Packard)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Personal Digital Assistant (PDA, Electronic Organizer)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Pocket PC (PCs)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Hewlett-Packard (Hewlett, Packard, HP)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handheld (Hand Held)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
      </BrowseList>
      <Media>Electronics</Media>
      <NumberofItems>1</NumberofItems>
      <Features>
         <Feature>Easy-to-use screen protectors designed for the HP Jornada 545</Feature>
         <Feature>Protect your HP Jornada 545's color screen</Feature>
         <Feature>A simple, inexpensive way to preserve the life of your pocket PC</Feature>
         <Feature>Multipack lasts for months</Feature>
      </Features>
      <Availability>Special Order</Availability>
      <Upc>725184293085</Upc>
      <Reviews>
         <AverageRating>3.28947</AverageRating>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>3</Rating>
            <Summary>Good idea, but...</Summary>
            <Comment>Even when removing the green plastic from the screen protector, I still found two problems with it.&lt;P>1. It doesn't "stay put" on the screen. As another reviewer has mentioned, it can be challenging to write when your writing surface itself is not stationary. This just takes some getting used to, and isn't a big annoyance after a couple of days.&lt;P>2. It makes the Journada very difficult to see in outdoor lighting conditions. The plastic cover makes the screen much more glarey than before. Often times, the image becomes so washed-out that it is impossible to use without finding some shade. (Before, the screen was difficult to see outside, but not impossible).&lt;P>So, this is a great idea, but somewhat lacking in the execution. If you don't need to use the Journada in bright lighting conditions, or if you are very concerned about scratching the screen, then you should probably buy these. Otherwise, steer clear.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>4</Rating>
            <Summary>Useful and Easy</Summary>
            <Comment>These little inserts work quite well. After removing the film from both sides the hard plastic piece just snaps right in. When the unit is on I don't see any screen quality degradation at all. When the unit is off I do see minor scuffs and scratches quickly but that is what the protector is there for. The size is almost perfect, maybe a fraction to small as it moves just a bit but not much. I have not found that it makes writing recognition or dragging more difficult at all. A very useful and necessary accessory to any 520 or 540 series Jornada.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>They work just fine!!</Summary>
            <Comment>All I can say is that I am more than satisfied with the HP Jornada screen protectors. I ordered them here on Amazon, I peeled off BOTH sides of the green tinted plastic sheets that protect the hard plastic screen protector and installed my first screen protector. I used the first one up in a few days, and was really disappointed, but with the second one (it's been on for a month) I used a different stylus....this has made all the difference!! There are many styli on the market, and I now own three...I have found that these don't scratch the screen protector as much as the original stylus.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
      </Reviews>
      <Similarities>
         <Similarity>B00004T2LJ</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004SPBV</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004SPBU</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00003G1RG</Similarity>
         <Similarity>0750673540</Similarity>
      </Similarities>
   </Details>
   <Details url="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=test&amp;creative=9441&amp;camp=1793&amp;link_code=xm2&amp;path=ASIN/B00005O7MW">
      <Asin>B00005O7MW</Asin>
      <ProductName>Hewlett Packard Jornada 568</ProductName>
      <Catalog>Electronics</Catalog>
      <Manufacturer>Hewlett Packard</Manufacturer>
      <ImageUrlSmall>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005O7MW.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlSmall>
      <ImageUrlMedium>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005O7MW.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlMedium>
      <ImageUrlLarge>http://images.amazon.com/images/P/B00005O7MW.01.LZZZZZZZ.jpg</ImageUrlLarge>
      <ListPrice>$599.94</ListPrice>
      <OurPrice>$549.94</OurPrice>
      <UsedPrice>$319.00</UsedPrice>
      <SalesRank>1,498</SalesRank>
      <BrowseList>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>HP</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Hewlett Packard (Hewlett-Packard)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Personal Digital Assistant (PDA, Electronic Organizer)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Pocket PC (PCs)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Hewlett-Packard (Hewlett, Packard, HP)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Handheld (Hand Held)</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
         <BrowseNode>
            <BrowseName>Casio</BrowseName>
         </BrowseNode>
      </BrowseList>
      <Media>Electronics</Media>
      <NumberofItems>1</NumberofItems>
      <Features>
         <Feature>Color Pocket PC with 64 MB of RAM with Microsoft's Pocket PC 2002 operating</Feature>
         <Feature>Built-in CompactFlash slot lets you add memory, accessories</Feature>
         <Feature>Vibrant 16-bit color display provides clear view indoors and out</Feature>
         <Feature>Rechargeable lithium-polymer battery lasts 14 hours</Feature>
         <Feature>Store and edit data, browse the Internet, check e-mail with powerful Pocket PC applications</Feature>
      </Features>
      <Platform>Windows 2000</Platform>
      <Availability>Available</Availability>
      <Upc>088698383803</Upc>
      <Accessories>
         <Accessory>B00005V6FB</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005V6F4</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005V6F5</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005V6F7</Accessory>
         <Accessory>B00005V6F9</Accessory>
      </Accessories>
      <Reviews>
         <AverageRating>4.41463</AverageRating>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>Glad I bought it</Summary>
            <Comment>Pros:&lt;BR>1. Nice, bright screen with fantastic resolution.&lt;BR>2. Stout body, nice protective flip cover.&lt;BR>3. Flashing LED for alarm notice&lt;BR>4. Ability to record audio and insert clips into Word documents.&lt;BR>5. Quick when running applications&lt;BR>6. Good battery time&lt;P>Cons:&lt;BR>1. Flimsy stylus (you'll want to buy one that's more like a pen)&lt;BR>2. Wish there was a jack for an external microphone&lt;BR>3. Locked up on me once and had to hit reset button&lt;BR>4. This baby costs $600!</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>5</Rating>
            <Summary>Great PDA and service -- so sad it's going away</Summary>
            <Comment>I love my Jornada 568! HP did just about everything right when designing the 560 series. I especially appreciate the flip-top, which protects your screen from scratches from car keys, pens, and other sharp objects in your pocket or purse. And HP's customer service was, for me, wonderful. (I don't hear many compliments for Compac's customer support crew. Read some the comments for the iPaq.)&lt;P>Unfortunately, with the HP-Compac merger, the powers running the show decided to discontinue the HP line of PDAs after this year. What a loss.&lt;P>My two minor gripes with the 568: compact flash slot doesn't support Type II (but you can easily remedy that by buying the CF Pocket 560 expansion sleeve), and I had the screen dust problem with my original 568 (production problem where dust gets behind the screen; annoying with dark backgrounds when the dust "lights up" like tiny stars on the screen). HP sent me a replacement 568, no questions asked. No problems with the newer unit.&lt;P>Bottom line: If you're looking to buy a Pocket PC 2002 PDA, buy the Jornada 568 -- while you still can!</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
         <CustomerReview>
            <Rating>2</Rating>
            <Summary>Upgrade was a downgrade</Summary>
            <Comment>I had a 548 and upgraded to the 568. Overall I liked the device but the issue with the screen filling with dust negates everything else. I had to replace it once but the new one is slowly accumulating a dust layer under the screen and that's with it kept in a zippered case whenever it's not in use. I would have replaced it again but it means reinstalling all software and ebooks and everything else I've added. I didn't even check the competition before buying this because I was so happy with my 548, I won't be replacing this one with an HP product. Very dissapointed.</Comment>
         </CustomerReview>
      </Reviews>
      <Similarities>
         <Similarity>B00005V6FC</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00004T2LJ</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005AC8J</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B00005V5T1</Similarity>
         <Similarity>B000059TF8</Similarity>
      </Similarities>
   </Details>
</ProductInfo>
